[
{
	"id": "1",
	"question": "If you throw me out of a window, you’ll leave a grieving wife. If you leave me in the middle of the door, you might just save a life. What am I?",
	"right_option": "The letter \"N\".",
	"option1": "The letter \"E\".",
	"option2": "The letter \"B\".",
	"option3": "The letter \"Q\"."
},
{
	"id": "2",
	"question": "What question can someone ask all day long, always get totally different answers, and yet all the answers could be correct?",
	"right_option": "What time is it?",
	"option1": "How are you?",
	"option2": "What is the weather today?",
	"option3": "Doesn't it look cool?"
},
{
	"id": "3",
	"question": "Which insect is the smallest?",
	"right_option": "Ant",
	"option1": "Bee",
	"option2": "Butterfly",
	"option3": "Spider"
},
{
	"id": "4",
	"question": "What day it is on the third day of the week if the week starts with Tuesday?",
	"right_option": "Thursday",
	"option1": "Monday",
	"option2": "Holiday",
	"option3": "Summer day"
},
{
	"id": "5",
	"question": "Why do we stop when the traffic light turns red?",
	"right_option": "Because we obey the traffic rule.",
	"option1": "Because it's fun.",
	"option2": "Because we decide to show off at the intersection.",
	"option3": "Because we want to take a rest."
},
{
	"id": "6",
	"question": "How many consonants are there in the English alphabet?",
	"right_option": "21",
	"option1": "22",
	"option2": "20",
	"option3": "31"
},
{
	"id": "7",
	"question": "What is the Italian word for pie?",
	"right_option": "Pizza",
	"option1": "Pipe",
	"option2": "Pip",
	"option3": "Peach"
},
{
	"id": "8",
	"question": "What grows quicker?",
	"right_option": "Hair",
	"option1": "Toenails",
	"option2": "Finger",
	"option3": "Head"
},
{
	"id": "9",
	"question": "After you go through a fall I will take over. All life will stall, or at least grow slower. What am I?",
	"right_option": "Winter",
	"option1": "Faith",
	"option2": "Perseverance",
	"option3": "Insubordination"
},
{
	"id": "10",
	"question": "Name the French novelist and poet, born in 1802, who was exiled to Jersey and who wrote about a hunchback.",
	"right_option": "Victor Hugo",
	"option1": "Colette",
	"option2": "Marcel Proust",
	"option3": "George Sand"
},
{
	"id": "11",
	"question": "What takes place in Hong Kong's Happy Valley?",
	"right_option": "Horse racing",
	"option1": "Horse flying",
	"option2": "Horse eating",
	"option3": "horse jumping"
},
{
	"id": "12",
	"question": "Which reptile, according to the song, should you never smile at?",
	"right_option": "Crocodile",
	"option1": "Chameleon",
	"option2": "Turtle",
	"option3": "Snake"
},
{
	"id": "13",
	"question": "Which Saint’s Day is celebrated on 14th February?",
	"right_option": "Saint Valentine",
	"option1": "Christmas",
	"option2": "New Year",
	"option3": "Saint Holiday"
},
{
	"id": "14",
	"question": "In which ocean did the famous Titanic sink in 1912?",
	"right_option": "North Atlantic Ocean",
	"option1": "pacific Ocean",
	"option2": "Ocean Habitat",
	"option3": "Mediterranean"
},
{
	"id": "15",
	"question": "Which two parts of the body continue to grow for your entire life?",
	"right_option": "Nose and ears",
	"option1": "Head and hand",
	"option2": "Mouth and eyes",
	"option3": "Heart and soul"
},
{
	"id": "16",
	"question": "What has 13 hearts but no organs?",
	"right_option": "A deck of cards",
	"option1": "A demon from hell",
	"option2": "A monster",
	"option3": "An angel from heaven"
},
{
	"id": "17",
	"question": "I can bring a smile to your face, a tear to your eye, or even a thought to your mind. But, I can’t be seen. What am I?",
	"right_option": "A Memory",
	"option1": "A gust of wind",
	"option2": "A smile",
	"option3": "A glance"
},
{
	"id": "18",
	"question": "I can be made and I can be played. I can be cracked and I can be told. What am I?",
	"right_option": "A joke",
	"option1": "A game",
	"option2": "A story",
	"option3": "A portrait"
},
{
	"id": "19",
	"question": "What is the next number in the following sequence– 7, 14, 21, 28?",
	"right_option": "35",
	"option1": "20",
	"option2": "17",
	"option3": "42"
},
{
	"id": "20",
	"question": "What makes up (approx.) 80% of our brain’s volume?",
	"right_option": "Water",
	"option1": "Skin",
	"option2": "Bone",
	"option3": "Blood"
},
{
	"id": "21",
	"question": "How many months do we have in a year?",
	"right_option": "12 months",
	"option1": "2 months",
	"option2": "120 months",
	"option3": "20 months"
},
{
	"id": "22",
	"question": "How many colors are there in a rainbow?",
	"right_option": "7",
	"option1": "8",
	"option2": "9",
	"option3": "10"
},
{
	"id": "23",
	"question": " Without fingers I point, without arms I strike, without feet I run. What am I?",
	"right_option": "A clock.",
	"option1": "A rock.",
	"option2": "A wheel.",
	"option3": "A Pen."
},
{
	"id": "24",
	"question": " How many days are there in a year?",
	"right_option": "365 days",
	"option1": "265 days",
	"option2": "465 days",
	"option3": "165 days"
},
{
	"id": "25",
	"question": "What is the answer of this difficult math question?\n 2 * 3 - 3 = ?",
	"right_option": "3",
	"option1": "2",
	"option2": "0",
	"option3": "1"
},
{
	"id": "26",
	"question": "Info.cern.ch is famous for being what?",
	"right_option": "The world's very first website.",
	"option1": "The world's very first chat room.",
	"option2": "The world's very first company.",
	"option3": "The world's very first develop team."
},
{
	"id": "27",
	"question": " I'm strong as a rock, but a word can destroy me. What am I?",
	"right_option": "Silence",
	"option1": "Love",
	"option2": "Hate",
	"option3": "Freedom"
},
{
	"id": "28",
	"question": "I'm called thick when close to the ground, but people smile when I'm high. What am I?",
	"right_option": "A cloud.",
	"option1": "A bird.",
	"option2": "A umbrella",
	"option3": "A airplane."
},
{
	"id": "29",
	"question": "The more you cut me the bigger I grow. What am I?",
	"right_option": "A Hole",
	"option1": "A Paper",
	"option2": "A hope",
	"option3": "A key"
}
]
